export default data = [
  {
      question: "Listen! The baby ______ in the bedroom. Why don’t you go in and take a look?",
      options: ["cried","cries","is crying","will cry"],
      correct_option: "is crying"
  },
  {
      question: "Jill is ______ that the city park is closed for the music festival because now she can’t jog there",
      options: ["excited","proud","scared","unhappy"],
      correct_option: "unhappy"
  },
  {
      question: "Steven wants to be a ______, because he loves to watch people enjoy the food he prepares",
      options: ["cook","doctor","driver","farmer"],
      correct_option: "cook"
  },
  {
      question: "Paul misses his parents a lot. He ______ them since he came to work in Taiwan a year ago",
      options: ["didn’t see","doesn’t see","hasn’t seen","won’t see"],
      correct_option: "hasn’t seen"
  },
  {
      question: "Our teacher Ms. Wu seldom laughs, but when she ______ , everyone in the same building can hear her",
      options: ["can","does","has","will"],
      correct_option: "does"
  },
  {
      question: "My sister is coming to my home today. She ______ with me for a week",
      options: ["stays","stayed","has stayed","will stay"],
      correct_option: "will stay"
  },
  {
      question: "Edward had worked as a computer engineer for ten years. This ______ helped him a lot when he started his own computer shop",
      options: ["chance","experience","hobby","knowledge"],
      correct_option: "experience"
  },
  {
      question: "If you’re interested in our business plan, ______ this number and ask for Ms. Lee. She’ll answer your questions",
      options: ["calling","call","and call","to call"],
      correct_option: "call"
  },
  {
      question: "Jimmy would not get up for breakfast, ______ his dad had already tried to pull him from his bed several times",
      options: ["although","because","if","until"],
      correct_option: "although"
  },
  {
      question: "Duncan spent all his money trying to ______ the bookstore his mom left him. Sadly, the business never got better, and he had to close it in the end",
      options: ["build","buy","save","start"],
      correct_option: "save"
  },
  {
      question: "Fiona loves listening to her children sing songs ______ at school",
      options: ["are learned","that learned","they learned","that they are learned"],
      correct_option: "they learned"
  },
  {
      question: "Beverly eats lots of snacks ______ meals. That’s why she is often too full to eat anything at mealtimes",
      options: ["after","between","during","from"],
      correct_option: "between"
  },
  {
      question: "Nora: Can I check your drawer for some tools we can use? Matt: Sure. Take a look. See if you can find ______ in there",
      options: ["any","it","others","those"],
      correct_option: "any"
  },
]
